In my garden, lilies
of the valley and periwinkle grow,
and in the wild,
yellow bells and
buttercups.  As you well
know, this is my
favorite time of year.  I
could spend the
whole day dancing
in the flower meadows and
watching my
tulips peek out
of the ground.  But we have to
work.  So
today I allow
myself only short
walks to
explore this new
world, hidden for so long by
winter, while
looking out for
elves, of course.
Yellow bells and
poppy seeds, hear the
whisper of the breeze and
dare to put down
curious roots.
They come and
awaken the frost, the
flash of spring that will
soon be erased from
memory, and a
heart full of hope that
awaits a tender
beginning again.
I recently
came across a wonderful
line in a book.  There
was a question: "Who
would you be if there was
no fear in your heart
?"  If I lived
without worrying about things I
can't
control, without
fear of failure, without
fear of myself,
how would I live and who would
I be like?  I
like to think
that I am on my way to
becoming that
person.  I noticed
that for me, the key to
this courage was
accepting the fact
that, in a general sense, there
are many things in my life that I
cannot control
.
For example, I can
try to take care of
myself,
eat well, and
exercise.  And
while these are great things
for me, I still wo
n't always
feel my
best.  I will be
sick.  Maybe
I won't even have
the privilege of growing old.  I
really don't know what's
going to happen, and it's
quite scary sometimes.  But it's
much scarier, in my opinion
, to live
life trying
to control something I ca
n't.  For me, it felt like a
gradual
release from the
habits I
relied on to
feel more in
control of my life
than I actually was
.  A very wise
man once told
me: to find yourself, you
must stop and
enter the inner
room of your spirit.
You should lock
the door because this experience may
not always be
pleasant and you
will be tempted to leave.
But after you
slowly work through
what needs attention,
you will be left with the
seed of something
special.  This seed is
you, the truth.  And that's
where you find your
strength.  No.  I hope
I brought
you a moment of peace or
reflection today, and I
send you all my
love.  By the way,
I recently found
some old
prints that I used to
sell in limited
editions in my
Etsy shop.  There were
a few that I
printed with
mistakes, and unfortunately,
this faint
line remained on the back of the prints.  As a result, I did
n't sell them.  However, I
thought it would be a
waste to
just throw them away.
So I decided to add
them to the flower lot
in my store,
hoping to find
owners for them
among those who are not
embarrassed by minor
flaws.  I don't have
many of them, but I
wanted to let
you know, just in case,
and I appreciate your
support of my
work as an artist.
This means everything to me
.  Thank you very much.
Sir, that's very rude.
It's still very
rude.  Lately
I've been drinking this tea every day.  These are
lavender, chamomile,
oatmeal, and hops.  It's an
interesting combination, but
it's so calming.  And,
of course, the best
part of tea drinking is
holding the cup in your
hands, it's so
warm.  Spring has come.
I am incredibly happy.
This morning I
went to the poplar trees by
the river and picked up
many small
buds that were just
opening at the
tips of the branches.  If
you collect these buds,
insist them on oil,
then in about 8
months you will get
poplar oil, which
can be
used for
healing ointment and
many other things.
Of course, I like to take
quite a bit where there are
plenty of trees, so I
gathered about two
dozen buds,
soaked them in oil, and look forward to
sharing the recipe
in the future.  I
also shot this
video over
many days, and the
weather was
a little different each time.  So I
was dressed a little differently
, and it was
funny because on
the last day I
climbed a
fallen tree, and when I was coming down,
my dress got caught
on a branch and I almost
fell over.  So I'm really
glad I don't have any
bruises or scratches
from that little
accident.  As you can see,
walks in the woods
can sometimes be
a bit dangerous and
eventful.
So, thank you again.
Sending you lots of
love and
see you very soon.  See you later.